mobrog.com 2019-08-15

# MOBROG Privacy Policy

We would sincerely like to thank you for your interest in taking part in genuine market research. We would like to share with you more about our policies on privacy, which we review on a regular basis and update on this page as necessary.

This website ("Site") and service ("Service") is owned and maintained by SPLENDID RESEARCH GmbH, Germany (referred to hereafter as “MOBROG”).

This privacy policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions.

This policy explains what information MOBROG collects about Members of the Site and how we use this information.

The MOBROG member program is operated as a survey panel for individuals who voluntarily register on the Site ("Members"). The Member can participate at offered surveys connected to the service and operated by MOBROG or third parties. Under certain conditions Members may be rewarded in money ("Rewards") for participating in certain activities such as completing surveys. 

###  1\. Collection and Use of Personal Information

MOBROG only collects and stores such information that is

\- mandatory Member information during the registration process (email address, password, nickname, year of birth, gender, postcode, education level and occupation status) or  
\- information given voluntarily by you in response to specific information requests in your Member profile (Further profiling).

MOBROG only collects information that is necessary for us to perform our business and provide the Service to you.

We will not share your personal information (name, nickname, address, email address, or phone number(s)) with any third party except as set forth in this privacy policy or unless you have given us your explicit prior consent.

For payout purposes we cooperate with the following companies:

* \- PayPal S.à.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A. 22-24 Boulevard Royal, L-2449 Luxembourg
\- Skrill Ltd. in 25 Canada Square, E14 5LQ London, United Kingdom

You accept the forwarding of your data for payout purposes. For these purposes your E-Mail address and in some cases your mobile phone number is needed.

You explicitly agree that we may share personal information through an identification number including e.g. year of birth, postal code, gender, education level and occupation status, as well as other personal information with other market research companies for the purpose of identifying third party survey opportunities that you may be eligible for.

  If you are eligible for a survey opportunity, the third party market research company will provide an identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the survey. If you have any questions about this data sharing please contact our support using our contact form.

We may host information request forms on behalf of our clients. These forms will clearly identify the identity and contact details of the organization collecting the information, and the information you provide will be managed according to the privacy policy of that third party. In the event that you complete a web form hosted by us, we will only disclose the specific information provided by you to that specific third party.

With the exceptions listed above, we WILL NOT disclose your information to any third party without your permission unless such action is necessary to:

a. Fulfill our obligations from the contract and provide the Service to you;  
b. Conform to legal requirements or comply with a legal procedure;  
c. Enforce the MOBROG Terms and Conditions in an orderly manner;

We may access your account, including its contents, under the circumstances stated above or for the purpose of responding to Service inquiries or resolving technical problems.

We may also share your personal information and/or social-demographic information, including, without limitation, a unique identification number (“UID”), postal code, gender, marital status, education, ethnicity/race (where permitted by applicable law), employment related information, and non-personally identifiable information on household members, with third party sample/market research companies (individually each a “Third Party MR Company” and collectively the “Third Party MR Companies”) for the purpose of identifying survey opportunities that you may be eligible for through the Third Party MR Companies. If you are eligible for a survey opportunity, the Third Party MR Company will provide your unique identification number and a survey link to us and we will invite you to participate in the survey. We will not share your name, email address, or phone number with the Third Party MR Companies. In connection with the sharing of your information with a Third Party MR Company, your information may be transferred and stored outside of your country of residence, including, without limitation, in the United States. If you have any questions about this data sharing please contact us or alternatively you can opt-out by closing your membership. Your participation in such survey opportunities does not entitle you to any benefits offered by, or membership with, the Third Party MR Companies.

###  2\. Use of other Information

a. MOBROG may create general aggregate data (such as age groups, interest profiles, geographic regions and other non-identifying information) about our Members and make it available to existing and potential advertisers, business partners and investors. This aggregate data never contains specific identifiable information about any individual user.

b. IP Address - The MOBROG servers automatically record the first block of your IP address, your browser type and operating system when you access our site. We may use this information to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our web site and compile aggregate user information for our advertisers.

c. Advertising-ID (IDFA) – By downloading our Application on your device we will track an Advertising-ID (IDFA), which was created by your device. IDFA is device-independent und can be used by us or our partners for identifying purposes. Depending on your operating system of your device you can set back this ID. We are using this data according to our privacy policy.

d. Cookies - MOBROG uses Cookies to personalize your experience and identify you when you are logged in to our site and/or participate in our surveys or any other survey of our partner companies. We may also use cookies so you can participate in surveys regarding specific ads and promotions you view while browsing the web. To facilitate the completion of these surveys, certain third party research firms may write, set, or read cookies, locally shared/stored objects, flash cookies, and/or any other related technology. If you participate, you may be re-contacted about the online ad or promotion and the market research firm will use the third party technology to determine whether you have seen, clicked on, or otherwise interacted with the online ad or promotion. If you have interacted with the online ad or promotion, the market research firm or their partners will provide you with the opportunity to complete the survey through MOBROG. If you do not wish to participate in this program, you are able to unsubscribe from the MOBROG website and Third Party Technologies will not be set in your browser.

If you do not want us to use cookies then you can easily stop them, or be notified when they are being used, by configuring your browser. If you do not allow cookies to be used some of our website might not work for you.  
Below please find a list of the cookies set or deployed by MOBROG and/or any third party research firms in connection with the Services. For the cookies with an opt-out mechanism, you can opt-out by clicking on the link provided below. For certain cookies no opt-out mechanism is provided.

**Name** |  **Purpose** |  **Consent**  
---|---|---  
464ad15045c8654cf3427a7d84d394d0 |  Display the proper language |  no opt-out provided  
b152bcd523eabb208a654ad4c7093d6d |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
keyingress_p |  Session cookie |  no opt-out provided  
__atuvc |  Social Media sharing |  no opt-out provided  
cbcdfp |  Cint unique respondents |  no opt-out provided  
_session_id |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
ASP.NET_SessionId |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
cint_forms_identity |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
cint_session_id |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
CintRespondent |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
ASPSESSIONIDQSAASRTD |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
PublicPanelistTicket |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
__utma |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
__utmb |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
__utmc |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
__utmv |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
__utmz |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
__hstc |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
__hssrc |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
__hssc |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
hsfirstvisit |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
hubspotutk |  Website usage statistics |  no opt-out provided  
NRAGENT |  System monitoring |  no opt-out provided  
flch |  Nebu DubInterviewer Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
flv |  Nebu DubInterviewer Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
flvsn |  Nebu DubInterviewer Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
flvuf |  Nebu DubInterviewer Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
sfcRelevantId |  Imperium RelevantID |  no opt-out provided  
RVCOOKIE |  Imperium RelevantID |  no opt-out provided  
RVIDExtId |  Imperium RelevantID |  no opt-out provided  
__EC_TEST__ |  Imperium RelevantID |  no opt-out provided  
ISIStest |  Imperium RelevantID |  no opt-out provided  
thx_guid |  ThreatMetrix |  no opt-out provided  
.SSI-ASPXAUTH |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
ASP.NET_SessionId |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
PHPSESSID |  Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
ANYSSIDOMAIN#lang |  Display the proper language |  no opt-out provided  
JSESSIONID |  NewRelic Performance Monitoring - Session Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
PHPSESSID |  FraudLogix Fraud Prevention |  no opt-out provided  
InnovateMR |  Online Ad Effectiveness Program |  no opt-out provided  
Session |  Session cookie |  no opt-out provided  
dkp___id |  DubKnowledgeRouting |  no opt-out provided  
Google Analytics |  Ad Targeting, Analytics/Measurement, Optimization |  no opt-out provided  
Comscore |  Online Ad Effectiveness Program |  no opt-out provided  
Dynamic Logic |  Online Ad Effectiveness Program |  no opt-out provided  
Facebook for Developers |  Online Ad Effectiveness Program |  no opt-out provided  
GWI |  Online Ad Effectiveness, Tracking Website Visits, Developing Online Look-a-Like Cohorts and Audience Insights |  no opt-out provided  
HotTraffic/DMAi |  Online Ad Effectiveness, Tracking Website Visits, Developing Online Look-a-Like Cohorts and Audience Insights |  no opt-out provided  
InsightExpress |  Online Ad Effectiveness Program |  no opt-out provided  
Nielsen |  Online Ad Effectiveness Program |  no opt-out provided  
Publicis |  Online Ad Effectiveness, Tracking Website Visits, Developing Online Look-a-Like Cohorts and Audience Insights |  no opt-out provided  
Quantcast |  Development of online “look alike” cohorts and audience insights |  no opt-out provided  
Liveramp |  Developing Online Look-a-Like Cohorts and Audience Insights |  no opt-out provided  
YouTube |  Ad Targeting |  no opt-out provided  
loginpanelingressregistration |  Registration Cookie |  no opt-out provided  
  
###  3\. Data Security

Information collected by MOBROG is stored in accordance with our site security policy and we take reasonable steps to ensure that Member information is secure from unauthorized access, interference and loss, modification or disclosure. If MOBROG no longer requires a specific information, we will take reasonable steps to destroy such information. 

###  4\. Access & Correction

Information collected by MOBROG can be accessed and updated by the Member by using the facility provided on the Site (you will be required to log in first). Furthermore you can contact MOBROG Support anytime and ask for any stored information concerning you. You can easily request deletion of your information by opting-out as described below. 

###  5\. Linked Sites

The MOBROG Site, the survey invitations we send you, and if applicable, the email promotions we send you may provide links to our partner and advertiser web sites. If you link to any of these Third Party sites this policy will not apply to your use of those sites. 

###  6\. Frequency of email communications

All email communications that result from your MOBROG membership will be sent directly from us and will prominently feature the MOBROG logo and our contact details. Except PayPal, none of our partner companies will contact you. After completing a given survey, you may experience a gap of some number of days before another survey invitation is offered. While every attempt is made to send each Member survey invitations frequently, due to various factors, a given Member may not receive as many invitations to participate in surveys as they would like. Note that MOBROG is under no obligation to offer any specific or minimum number of survey invitations whatsoever. 

###  7\. Opting out

As a condition of membership, you must provide a valid email address and agree to accept survey invitations from us.

If you do not wish to receive survey invitations from us, you must terminate your membership using the facility provided in the profile. A link to an opt-out facility is also provided at the bottom of every survey invitation we send you (you will be required to log in first). By following this link you may terminate your membership.

In the event that you opt-out it may take up to 72 hours for your opt-out request to take effect. You will not receive any further email promotions from us after that time.

Your account will become inactive for and permanently deleted after seven days except from such data that has to be archived for legal reasons. After that, all personally identifiable information will be destroyed. This also affects any outstanding or undelivered rewards due. If you want to reverse your membership termination within these seven days, please contact our support.

###  8\. Changes to this policy

MOBROG reserves the right to update this policy from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).  If you do not agree with this privacy policy in completely or in part, or if you do not agree with changes made to this policy, you must not become a member or terminate your account.
